A Guide to the John Wells research notes, 1871-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
John Wells Research Notes, 1871-2006
The Library of Virginia
43293
26.7 cu. ft.
John Emory Wells
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Lynwood D. Wells on 28 June 2007
Biographical Information
Born in Martinsville, Virginia, on August 17, 1954, John Emory Wells (1954-2007), was the son of Rev. Lynwood D. Wells Sr. of Martinsville, Virginia, and Mary Jay Speer Wells. He was a graduate of Martinsville High School and the University of Virginia School of Architecture. Wells was employed by the Virginia Landmarks Division from 1985 to 2000 as an Architectural Historian and by the Virginia Department of Transportation (VDOT) as a District Preservation Manager from 2000 until his death in 2007. John Wells also co-authored two books on architectural history, The Virginia Architects, 1835-1955 and The South Carolina Architects, 1885-1935.
Scope and Content
Research notes, 1871-2006, of architectural historian John Emory Wells (1954-2007) of Richmond, Virginia. The collection is principally comprised of materials collected by Wells from which he used to co-author two biographical dictionaries, entitled The Virginia Architects, 1835-1955 and The South Carolina Architects, 1885-1935. The collection also contains notes on architects who practiced in several other states, these include Alabama, Arkansas, District of Columbia (DC), Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Maryland, Mississippi, Missouri, North Carolina, Texas, and West Virginia. The collection also includes a large extent of notes from the Manufacturer's Record, as well as many other documents, including clippings, correspondence, notes, photographs, and architectural drawings.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Architect lists and card files, n.d.
Series II. Manufacturers Record, 1890-1948
Series III. Miscellaneous notes, 1871-2006
Series IV. Architectural drawings, 1906-1982
Contents List
- Series I. Architect lists and card files, n.d., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 1-15c)
  Series I. includes lists of architects taken from newspaper clippings, city directories, and other publications. These lists include architects who practiced in the following states: Alabama, Arkansas, District of Columbia (DC), Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Maryland, Mississippi, Missouri, North Carolina, South Carolina, Texas, Virginia, and West Virginia.
  Arranged alphabetically by architect within each state.
  - Anderson, Frank Hartley (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Joe Y. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ausfeld, Frederick (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ayers, C.M. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Black, H.H. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brodie, T.L. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Downey, A.H. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Duncan, Samuel A. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Galliher, C. Frank (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Green, J.E. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Halstead, Jackson C. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hawkins, H.W. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Holmes & Schmidt (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Horton, W.A. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hunt, R.H. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hutchisson, C.L. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lide, Martin J. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lockwood, Frank (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lockwood, _ (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Malone, C.E. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - McKeil, John W. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Myers, C.M. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Persey, L.H. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Poundstone, _ (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Price, Bem (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Roberts, J.L. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Salie, J.E. (Alabama) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Abbott, John Benjamin (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Abt, Ludwig (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Agee, P.W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aldrich, Albert P. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Allaire, William (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Allen, R.N. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Althus, Jacob (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Anderson, _ (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Anderson, Bruce Roy (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Anderson, Verne A. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Armstron, A.J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Atkinson, B.A. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bailey, Paul C. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bailey, W.T. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Baker, George D. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Baldwin, Mathias H. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Baldwin, O.N. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bartlett, B.J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bartling, George R. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bateman, J.S. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Beam, Peter K. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Beaty, C.N. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bennett, Carl (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bivens, John (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bobbet, T.J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bocage, Joseph W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Blackman, Pearle (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Blackshare, W.S. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bliss, Stanley W.(Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Blue, John (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Blye, J.R. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Boller, Carl (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Boon, _ (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Boone, H.R. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Boone, W.B. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bornell, George M. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bracy, Buford (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bradshaw, Preston J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Broadwell, James J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Brodie, T.J. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Brown, Arthur A. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Brown, B.R. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Brown, J.R. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bruce, Isaiah W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bruce, Thomas (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Burdsal, Clayton W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Burdsal, William (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Burnham, Franklin P. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Burrell, Seymour (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Burton, P.V. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Butcher, Perry L. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Byron, Charles (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Cairns, Bayard (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Caldwell, James L. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Cann, W.A. & Company (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Carter, Charles B. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Case, George (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Church, J.H. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Criner, J.C. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Cromwell, Edwin B. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Curran, B.F. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Davidson, Julian B. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Davis, W.W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Davis, William (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Dawson, Charles W. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Dillery, Samuel C. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Dinwiddie, James (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Donaway, Paul C. (Arkansas) (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Dorshay, F.J. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dougherty & Gardner (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Drewry, M.W. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ewens, Ed (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fancher, J.P. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ford, Thomas L. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Franklin, James G. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Friber, M.E. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Friedman, _ (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Frier, Thomas Sidney (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Friese, John (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Frink, Sidney M. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gage, W.A. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Goddard, Harry I. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Greathouse, W.E. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Greer, Matt F. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hendrick & Cochran (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Helton, W.S. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Houke, H.C. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Hudgins Brothers (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Jewett, Albert (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Johnson, Jay E. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, P.L. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Edward C. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Jones, R.H. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kellogg, C.W. & Son (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Kemper, Charles E. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - McConnell, Abraham (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - McGinnis, _ (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Montgomery, D.C. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Rains, Louis (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Rogers, B.K. (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Royse, E. Charles (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Young, William (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Architects, Florida (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Barry, Gerlad A. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bauman, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Benjamin, Roy A. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bergman, Phillip (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Biggers, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bliven, J.R. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bryan, Sheldon (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bryson, Joseph H. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Burroughs, H. Robins (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Butler, G.T. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Camp, W.B. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cates, Frederick S. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cellar, Eugene A. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Clementz, C.W. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Close, Bernard W. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cole, Albert N. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cummer, Wellington W. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Darsott, Wilbur (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Dougherty, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dozier, Henrietta Cuttino (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Drake, W. Kenyon (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Duffy, C.J. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Ehmann, E.A. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Fetner, S. Ralph (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Fox, C.H. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Gasser, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Greeley, Mellen C. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Greer, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Griffing, C.M. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Graveley, John (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Gilkes, A.B. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Hamilton, Sargent (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Hale, William C. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Hall, Edward E., Jr. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Hammond, W.G. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Harris, Clyde E. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Hawkins, J.W.H. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Hawoth, Albert (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Hills, G.B. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Holmes, George O. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Holmes, George O., Jr. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Holmes, Rutledge (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Hopkins, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Hopkins, Abner C. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Hopkins, John S. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Huber, Raymond (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Huddleston, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Kirton, M. Britton (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Klutho, Henry J. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Klyce, H.K. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Lankford, J.A. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Lookbaugh, H.C. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Lumberman's Plan Service (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - MacDonough, G.M. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Mark, V. Earl (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Marsh, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Marsh, W. Mulfod (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - McMarrel, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - McClure, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Messick, Homer (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Mitchell, Arthur J. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Morrison, H. Dunlap (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Nechodome, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Niederhauser, C.P. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Nippell, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Norton, Francis Joseph (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Oehme, Charles C. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Page, _ (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Talley, W.B. (Florida) (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Allcorn, George (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Archer, Edgar W. (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Ashley, E.H. (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Baxter, W.H. (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Benedict, Allen (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Boles, James M. (Kentucky) (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Boyle, Harry E. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Buffington, R.L. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bullock, John H. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Carrere & Hastings (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Churchill, H.A. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Colley, J. Mayrick (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Crowe & Schulte (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Crutcher, M.J. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Curtis, _ (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dailey, Alfred B. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Brinton B. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dean, L.J. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dohrman, George F. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Eaglehardt, N.L. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eberson, John. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Evans, _ (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fleenor, C.M. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fowler & Karges (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Frankel, _ (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - George & Zimmerman. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Harrington, A.C. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Hawick, O.C. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hendricks, J.W. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hoehle, George B. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Holing, Wallace (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hunter, _ (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hutchings, E.T. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jamieson, D. Harry (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Klein, Albert (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Oberwarth, Leo L. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Plato, Samuel M. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rabe, William A. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Stevens, Joseph. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Scofield, George W. (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Underwood, Robert (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Walker, Lyman (Kentucky) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Adams, E. Eugene (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Adams, O.E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Adams, Henry (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Ahrens, Theodore G. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Allen, Raymond P. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Allied Construction Company (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Anderson, Charles Montgomery (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Anderson, Clarence E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Archer, George (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Asbell, J.R. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Bacon, G. Summerfield (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Bailey, Elmer Smith (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Baldwin, F.E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Bashford, Askew (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Baltzell, Wesley (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Beall, Frederick E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Beardsley, W.J. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Beecher, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Beecher, W. Gordon (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Beecher, William G. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Berger, H.W. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Blanke, E.G. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bond, R.T. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Brauns, Henry (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Brinkloe, WIlliam David (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Brockmeyer, R.C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Brooks, Sanford (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Brower, J.B, Jr. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Buckler, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Butler, Wright (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cain, Herbert L. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Carrere & Hastings (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Case, Paul (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Cassell, Charles E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Clifford, Frank E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Crilley, Grover C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Crisp, H.G. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Corbin, Walter (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Crook, H.P., Jr. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Davis, Frank E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Davis, Henry (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Dodson, H.C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Doeleman, Herman P. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Downing, J.M. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Edwards, Robert & William (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Egli, Hans (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Elgin, Jacob F., Jr. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Elgin, Jacob F., Sr. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Ellicott, Willam M. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Emmart, William W. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Evans, A.F. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Fenhagen, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Fizone, W.J. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Forsythe, John R. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Frederick, George A. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Freund, John (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Friz, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Friz, Clyde N. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Friz, Nelson (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Gerwig, William B. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Ghequier, T. Butchler (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Gibson, B.K. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Glidden, Edward H. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gott, Jackson C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Gowell, Guy (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Green, G. Edw. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Gregg, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Haskell, George C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Hodges, William Hanson (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Kavanagh, Hugh I. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Kennedy, Thomas C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Kimball, S.P. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Kump, John C. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Laferty, J.E. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Lee, James W. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Lerch, R. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Levi, Louis. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Lockart, _ (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Lohmuller Building Company (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Mackenzie, George H. (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Magruder, Hugh (Maryland) (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Maryland Architects (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mason, Alfred (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - McLaughlin, James (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - McLaughlin, Robert (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Milburn, Heister & Company (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell, T.H. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Moris, George R. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nolting, William G. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Owens, Benjamin B. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Parker, J. Harleston (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Parker, _ (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Parrott, W.J. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pennington, Josias (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pietsch, Theo Wells (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rice, _ (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sackerman, Daniel (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sandlass, Richard C. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sansbury, George Flack (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sansbury, J.W. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Siebert, John S. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sill, Howard (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sisco, Spencer (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Smith, H.M. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Small, Jacob, Sr. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Smith, S.J. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Stevenson, R.M. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Sperry, Joseph E. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Thomas, _ (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Thomas, Douglas H. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Torney, Francis E. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Turnbull, Bayard (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Wilson, W.T. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Watson, Frank B. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Watte, Albert S. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Weisheit, J. Elmer (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Wessel, George (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Whert, L.P. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Wight, _ (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Wilson, J.A. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Wolcott, J. Winthrop (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Wolf, E.A. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Wood, R.H. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Woodrow, J.F. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Woodruff, S.H. (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Worthington, George (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Wyatt, J.B. Noel (Maryland) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Alsop, M.M. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Austin, H.N. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Bartlett & Thompson (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Berg, S.H. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Black, H.C. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Black, J.D. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Black, W.C. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bost, _ (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Brasher, William A., Jr. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Brewer, Samuel C. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Cline, Logan (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Collins, Amariah (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Davenport, James (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Davis, J.H. & Son (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Davis, Toots (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Dickey, D. Anderson (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Dobson, F.M. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Ford, Homer (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Fullington, D.E. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Gautier, Fernando Upton (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Glass, W.O. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Gibbon, William (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Grant, M.B. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Griffin, H.C. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Griffen, James S. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hardie, James (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hardy, H.K. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Harvey, T.J. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Harkness, W.T. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Horn, N.W. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Hull, Emmett J. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Hull, W.S. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Hunt, Reuben H. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Ingraham, Joseph Holt (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Jetsy, R. & Company (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, J.W. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Keenan & Weiss (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Ketteringham, G.W. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Kramer, X.A. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Laramour, J. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Laurance, John (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Lee, R.E. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Little Checker Construction Company (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Lull, James S. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Markel, Henry G. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Mayer, David (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - McClanahan, _ (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - McCormick, Eugene (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - McGee, W.J. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - McGeoy, Frank R. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Moulton, _ (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Mundy, Roy (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Parker, W.H. (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Pond, Charles (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Price, Bem (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Reynes, E. Mazurean (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Steitenroth, William (Mississippi) (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Stevens, Hardy (Mississippi) (Box 5, Folder 1)